Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
- Box: 50, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: De Koers Bepaalt de Vaart, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: Kongresverlag
  - Item 2: Le Taux de Sydicalisation en Belgique, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: Jean Neuville
    Notes: January 11, 1963
  - Item 3: Les Problemes de Structure Interne a la F.G.T.B., 1961; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: Centre de Recherche et D'Information Socio-Politiques -- C.R.I.S.P.
    Notes: June 16, 1961
  - Item 4: Le Syndicalisme Independent en Belgique, 1964; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: R. Gubbels
    Notes: May 22, 1964
  - Item 5: La Confederation des Syndicats Uniques et Apolitiques de Belgique, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Notes: July 15, 1966
  - Item 6: Les Elections Syndicales de 1967, 1968; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 8, 1968
  - Item 7: Les Elections Syndicales en Belgique, 1964; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Notes: January 17, 1964
  - Item 8: Le Taux de Syndicalisation en Belgique en 1966, 1968; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 23, 1968
  - Item 9: Le Renouvellement des Structures Internes de la F.G.T.B. et le Processus de Nomination du Secretaire General de la F.G.T.B., 1968; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Notes: October 11, 1968
  - Item 10: Le Taux de Syndicalisation en Belgique, 1967; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Notes: June 16, 1967
  - Item 11: Labor's Partnership in Industrial Enterprise, 1950; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: Alexander S. Lipsett
  - Item 12: Trade Unions and the Development of Physical Culture and Sports in the U.S.S.R., 1960; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: A. Vasilyev
    Notes: A. Vasilev
  - Item 13: Diversion of Union Welfare-Pension Funds of Allied Trades Council and Teamsters Local 815, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. Senate
    Notes: June 30, 1966
  - Item 14: Welfare and Pension Plan Protection Act of 1968, Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. House of Representatives
    Notes: September 5, 1968
  - Item 15: Employer Contributions for Child-Care Centers and Scholarships Under NLRA, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Notes: May 8, 1969
  - Item 16: Joint Labor-Management Trust Funds for Scholarships and Child Care Centers, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. Committee on Education and Labor
    Notes: May 7, 1969
- Box: 50, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Labor Movement in the United States, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Author: Mary R. Heslet
    Notes: August 7, 1963
- Box: 50, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Union Membership at New High in State, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Author: California Department of Industrial Relations
    Notes: January 30, 1966
- Box: 50, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions and Collective Bargaining in Canada, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Industrial and Geographic Distribution of Union Membership in Canada in 1969, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: The Role of International Unionism in Canada, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Author: Canadian-American Committee
  - Item 4: A Brief History of Canadian Labor, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Author: Clifford A. Scotton
- Box: 50, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Central Labor Union Activities, 1949; Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
    Author: University of Illinois
    Notes: November 29-30, 1949
- Box: 50, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Le Cheminement Parlementaire du Droit de Syndicalisation Dans les Services Publics, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
    Notes: April 8, 1966
- Box: 50, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Communist Party and the Trade Unions, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Author: Finlay Hart
  - Item 2: Communist in Labor Relations Today, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Author: Research Institute of America
  - Item 3: Communism in a Criminal Conspiracy, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Author: Senate Subcommittee on Internal Security
  - Item 4: The Peril in Our Midst, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Author: Woodrow Wyatt
  - Item 5: What to do About Communism in Unions, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Author: L.R. Boulware, G.H. Pfeif, W.J. Barron
  - Item 6: The Caterpillar Tractor Story, 1948; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Author: Opinion Research Corporation
  - Item 7: Die Spaltung der Arbeiterklasse und Der Weg Der Revolutionaren Gewerkschafts Opposition, 1929; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Author: Von Paul Merker
  - Item 8: Investigation of Communist Infiltration into the Fur Industry, 1948; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
    Notes: December 27, 1948
- Box: 50, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Leon Trotsky on the Trade Unions, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Author: Leon Trotsky
  - Item 2: The Trade Unions, 1961; Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Author: L.L. Sharkey
  - Item 3: Freedom is the Exeption, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
    Author: William C. Sullivan
- Box: 50, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: We're One Year Old and This is What We're Doing, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
    Author: University of Massachusetts
  - Item 2: The Time is Now, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Now We Are Two and This is What We're Doing, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Community Services Counseling Training for Greater Hartford Trade Unionists, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
    Notes: June 1966
- Box: 50, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Why Should Labor Be Concerned with Cooperatives, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
    Author: Jack McLanahan, Al Rightley
- Box: 50, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Handbook on Central Labor Bodies: Functions and Activities, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Author: Joan G. Kilpatrick, Miles C. Stanley
- Box: 50, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Achievement and Importance of the Trade Movement in the Social Life of Denmark, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Author: Eiler Jensen
  - Item 2: Hvorhen Gar Dansk Fagbevaigelse, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
    Author: Kai Moltke
    Language: Danish.
- Box: 50, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Building the Local Union Education Program, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Author: John J. Flagler
  - Item 2: AFL-CIO Scholarship Kit, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Author: Cornell University
  - Item 3: Training of Trades Union Officials, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Author: E.P. Harries
  - Item 4: Development of Educational Services for Trade Unionists, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Author: Trades Union Congress
  - Item 5: Using Education in Your Union, 1952; Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Manual Pare el Establecimiento de Institutos de Trabajo, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Author: Union Panamerica
  - Item 7: American Workers Education in Action, 1950; Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Author: Economic Cooperation Administration
    Notes: May 1950
  - Item 8: Unions Explore the United Nations, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Author: American Labor Education Service
  - Item 9: Long-Term Resident Programs for Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
    Author: Fred K. Hoehler
    Notes: April 17, 1963
- Box: 50, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Bill, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Manual of Workers' Education Techniques, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
    Author: U.S. International Cooperation Administration
- Box: 50, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Estonian Labour in Chains, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
    Author: Johannes Mihkelson
- Box: 50, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Unions in Europe, Publication (Box 50, Folder 19)
    Author: Eli Marx, Walter Kendall
  - Item 2: Topical Problems of the International Trade Union Movement, 1962; Publication (Box 50, Folder 19)
    Author: S. Vukmanovic Tempo
- Box: 50, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Financial Survey of the Major National and International Unions of the United States, Publication (Box 50, Folder 20)
    Author: Chamber of Commerce of the United States
  - Item 2: Problem Set in Accounting Methods for Local Unions, 1949; Publication (Box 50, Folder 20)
    Author: University of Minnesota
    Notes: January 1949
- Box: 50, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Position du Mouvement Syndical Force Ouvriere, Publication (Box 50, Folder 21)
    Author: M. Gabriel Ventejol
  - Item 2: La Participation des Syndicats Aux Organismes Officiels Menace-T-Elle Leur Independance?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 21)
    Author: Les Cahiers du Centre D'Etudes Socialistes
- Box: 50, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Cien Anos del Movimiento Laboral Aleman, Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
    Author: Centro de Estudios Sindicales
  - Item 2: Trade Union Rights in the GDR: Human Rights Put Into Practice, Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
    Author: Confederation of German Free Trade Unions
  - Item 3: Sozialistische Brigaden und ihr Kulturhaus, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Die Gewerkschaftlichen Rechtsberatungsstellen, Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Die Aufgaben der Deutschen Gewerkschaften in Wirtschaft, Staat und Gesellschaft, Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
    Author: Hans Buckler
  - Item 6: Die Information und ihre Bedeutung fur die Gewerkschaftliche Leitungstatigkeit, Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
    Author: Fuder, Schulz
  - Item 7: The Decisive Step, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
    Author: Tribune Trade Union Publishing House
  - Item 8: Democracy in the West German Trade Unions: A Reapprisal of the "Iron Law", Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
    Author: Richard J. Willey
  - Item 9: Industrial Relations in Germany, 1950; Publication (Box 50, Folder 22)
    Author: Great Britain Board of Trade
- Box: 50, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Actual Aims and Problems of German Trade Unions, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 23)
    Author: German Trade Union Federation
  - Item 2: Freedom of Association and the Relationship Between the Two Sides of Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 50, Folder 23)
    Author: Federal Ministry of Labour and the Social Structure
  - Item 3: Gewerkschaftliche Dynamik in Einer Sich Wandelnden Welt, 1965; Publication (Box 50, Folder 23)
    Author: Otto Brenner
  - Item 4: Rechtsfahigkeit und Verbandsverfassung, 1971; Publication (Box 50, Folder 23)
    Author: Friedrich Kubler
- Box: 50, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Industrial Advance, Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Author: Conservative Political Centre
  - Item 2: Trade Unions in Britain, Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Author: British Information Services
  - Item 3: The Structure and Organisation of British Trade Unions, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Author: PEP
    Notes: December 2, 1963
  - Item 4: Trade Unions in a Changing Society, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Notes: June 10, 1963
  - Item 5: Trade Unions and the Law, 1964; Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Notes: March 23, 1964
  - Item 6: Trade Unions in Britain, Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: New Unions for Old, 1961; Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Author: Roger Cuss, Maurice Gent, Trevor Smith
  - Item 8: Trade Unions for Tomorrow, Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: The Trade Union and the Community, Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Author: Tavistock Institute of Human Relations
  - Item 10: The Trade Union and the Common Weal, 1967; Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Author: Henry Phelps Brown
    Notes: June 7, 1967
  - Item 11: T.U.C. Centenary, Publication (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Author: National Book League
- Box: 50, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Growth of the Trade Union Movement, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: Trade Union Series
  - Item 2: Trade Unions and Communism, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Trade Union and Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Trade Unions Today, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: British Institute of Management
  - Item 5: The Trade Unionist in Britain, 1952; Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Notes: September 1952
  - Item 6: Trade Unionism, its Origins, Growth, and Role in Modern Society, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: Herbert Tracey
  - Item 7: Trade Unions in a Labour Britain, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: J.B. Jefferys
  - Item 8: Trade Unions in the New Era, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: Ben Roberts
  - Item 9: More About the Trade Unions, Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: David Clarke
  - Item 10: British Labour Movement, 1951; Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: G.D.H. Cole
    Notes: April 1951
  - Item 11: Abraham Lincoln and the Working Classes of Britain, 1959; Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: English Speaking Union
  - Item 12: Key Questions for Trade Unionists, 1960; Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: Jim Gardner
  - Item 13: Two Centuries of Trade Unionism, 1953; Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Item 14: The Trade Unionist and Full Employment, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 25)
    Author: John Vaizey
- Box: 50, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Strike of Bargain?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 26)
    Author: D.J. Williams
  - Item 2: The Alternative to Wilson, Publication (Box 50, Folder 26)
    Author: G. Healy
  - Item 3: The Early Trade Unions, Publication (Box 50, Folder 26)
    Author: Jackdaw Publications
  - Item 4: Trade Unions in Britain, Publication (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: The History of British Trade Unionism, 1969; Publication (Box 50, Folder 26)
    Author: R & E Frow, Michael Katanka
- Box: 50, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Letter to Victor Reuther, 1949; Publication (Box 50, Folder 27)
    Author: Strachan
    Notes: February 25, 1949
- Box: 50, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Norweigan Labor in Hawaii: the Norse Immigrants, Publication (Box 50, Folder 28)
    Author: Eleanor H., Carl D. Davis
  - Item 2: Labor Unions of Hawaii, Publication (Box 50, Folder 28)
    Author: John E. Reinecke
- Box: 50, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Los Angeles Conference on Health and Welfare, Publication (Box 50, Folder 29)
    Author: AFL
- Box: 50, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: A Szakszervezeti Nobizottsagok Munkaja, 1962; Publication (Box 50, Folder 30)
    Author: Soter Edit
    Language: Hungarian.
- Box: 50, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Industrial Unionism: A Critical Analysis, 1949; Publication (Box 50, Folder 31)
    Author: J.D.M. Bell
- Box: 50, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Atti Ufficiali, Publication (Box 50, Folder 32)
    Author: A Cura Della Sede Centrale
- Box: 50, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Productivity, Efficiency Wage Cost and Price Competitiveness of Japanese Exports in the 1950's, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 33)
    Author: Yoko Kawashima
  - Item 2: Labor Movement in Japan, 1958; Publication (Box 50, Folder 33)
    Author: Japan Federation of Employers' Associations
  - Item 3: The Trade Union Law of the People's Republic of China, Publication (Box 50, Folder 33)
    Author: Foreign Languages Press
  - Item 4: The Labor Union Movement in Postwar Japan, 1954; Publication (Box 50, Folder 33)
    Author: The Daily Labor Press
- Box: 50, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Role of the Trade Unions in the Alliance for Progress, 1962; Publication (Box 50, Folder 34)
    Author: Pan American Union
    Notes: August 20, 1962
- Box: 51, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Disciplinary Powers and Procedures in Union Constitutions, Publication (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Organised Labour and the Rise of Trade Unionism in Malaysia After World War II, 1970; Publication (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Author: P. Arudsothy
    Notes: October 12-30, 1970
- Box: 51, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report on Union Member Attitude Survey, Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Author: University of California, Berkeley
  - Item 2: Political Communication Patterns Among Union Members: The Case of the Toledo Auto Workers, Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Author: Schley R. Lyons, Norman Blume
  - Item 3: Participation: The Key to Union Effectiveness, 1966; Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Author: Frederick A. Zeller & Eugene C. Hagburg
- Box: 51, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Membership, 1965; Publication (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Author: Leo Troy
- Box: 51, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Large Gain in California Union Membership, 1965; Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
    Notes: February 5, 1965
- Box: 51, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations and The Social-Economic Council in the Netherlands, Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Author: The Social- Economic Council
  - Item 2: Statuten en Huishoudelijk Reglement, 1962; Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Author: Algemene Bedrijfsgroepen Centrale
    Notes: January 1962
- Box: 51, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Labor Organization in New Jersey, Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Box: 51, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Trade-Union Movement in Nigeria, Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Author: Daniel Door Achakpa
  - Item 2: Trade Union Development and Labor Relations in Nigeria, Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Author: Mathew Tokunboh
- Box: 51, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Innstilling om Organisasjonsrett, Organisasjonstvang og Organisasjonsmonopol I Norsk Arbeidsliv, 1966; Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
    Author: Trykt I Reklametrykk A.s
    Notes: January 20, 1966
- Box: 51, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: An Act to Amend Chapter 295 of the Revised Statutes, 1954, The Trade Union Act, 1964; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
    Author: Nova Scotia Legislature
    Notes: March 18, 1964
- Box: 51, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Electing Union Officers, 1967; Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Notes: February 1967
  - Item 2: Electing Union Officers, 1961; Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Electing Union Officers, 1970; Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Guia del Delegado de Taller, Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Author: U.S. Information Service
  - Item 5: Why I am in the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Author: National Planning Association
  - Item 6: Local Union Election Appeals, 1966; Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Notes: July 1966
  - Item 7: A Quantitative Appraisal of Presidential Turnover Rates Before and After the Landrum-Griffin Act, 1970; Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Author: Marvin Snowbarger, Sam Pintz
    Notes: June 1970
- Box: 51, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Unions as a Channel of Mobility in Communist China, 1969; Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
    Author: Paul Harper
    Notes: August 24-30, 1969
- Box: 51, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Writing the History of Hawaiian Labor Unions, 1967; Publication (Box 51, Folder 12)
    Author: Edward D. Beechert
    Notes: May 1967
- Box: 51, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Ground Rules for Labor and Management During Organizing Drives, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Author: Prentice- Hall
  - Item 2: What to Do When the Union Calls, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Author: Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry
  - Item 3: Winning and Election, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Author: American Association of Industrial Management
  - Item 4: The Independent Employee, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Author: Neal E. Drought
  - Item 5: Management Electioneering Guide, 1965; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Author: Richard J. Fritz
  - Item 6: Unionizing Steel, 1936; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Author: WM. Z. Foster
    Notes: August 1936
  - Item 7: Some Timely Legal Topics, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Author: South-Western Publishing Co.
  - Item 8: Labor Organization in the South, 1946; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Author: Kendrick Lee
    Notes: May 29, 1946
  - Item 9: Time as a Determinant of Union Election Success, 1969; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Author: U.S. National Labor Relations Board
- Box: 51, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Trade Union Movement in Norway, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Arbeidernes Faglige Landsorganisasjon I Norge
  - Item 2: Organized Labor in the Soviet Union, 1943; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Edwin S. Smith
  - Item 3: Trade Unionism in Malaya, 1954; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Alex Josey
  - Item 4: Draft of Model Rules for Trade Unions, 1938; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: P.G. Moskatov
  - Item 5: Japan's Labor Problems, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Ministry of Foreign Affairs
  - Item 6: Where We Stand, 1960; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: SOHYO
  - Item 7: The Truth About Yugoslav Trade Unions, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: History of Labor Federations in the Philippines, 1961; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Problems of Indian Trade Unionism and Labour Relations, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Van Dusen Kennedy
  - Item 10: Racialism and the Trade Unions, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Industrial Relations and Race Relations, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Guy Routh
  - Item 12: Trade Unions in South Africa, 1954; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Notes: March 1954
  - Item 13: Trade Unions in Travail, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Alex Hepple
  - Item 14: Labor Unions in the Far East, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Eleanor H. Lattimore
  - Item 15: A Manifesto of the Democratic Revolution, 1951; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Richard L-G. Deverall
  - Item 16: Labor and the Soviet System, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Romuald Szumski
  - Item 17: An Outline History of the New Zealand Labour Movement, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: The Cuban Trade Union Movement, 1960; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: ORIT- ICFTU
    Notes: October 1960
  - Item 19: The African Worker in South Africa, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 20: La Solidaridad de la ORIT Con los Trabajadores del Peru, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: ORIT
  - Item 21: Beroep en Roeping, Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Meidoornsingel
  - Item 22: A Trade Union Programme for Nigeria, 1948; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: E.A. Cowan
  - Item 23: The Strength of Trade Unionism in Scotland, 1950; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Item 24: African Trade Unions, 1949; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: W.S. Mare
  - Item 25: The Labor Movement in Egypt, 1955; Publication (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Author: Abdel Raouf Abou Alam